Companies will have to take in terms of how they launch or ultimately progress, you know,
medicines.
We're already in a situation where, depending on how you look, 30 to 40 percent of medicines
in Europe available in the U.S. don't ultimately come to Europe.
You could have that number grow.
In general, significant delays for introduction of medicines into the European Union.
So there's a lot of work to do.
We certainly have, I think, proposals to all the key governments and most important in
my mind are Japan and Germany.
But we haven't seen the progress that we need to see.
So this is something we'll have to continue to advocate for over the next year because
I think it's really a 2027 story where you start to see the impact of MFN on launches
in Europe.
Next question.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of James Gordon from Barclays.
Please go ahead.
Hello.
I'm James Gordon from Barclays.
Thanks for taking the question.
The question was on hormonal breast cancer.
So, you know, I think it's really important.
The question is, how do you know that you can get the right amount of the right amount
of MFN for breast cancer?
So what should we expect to have?
Chirogesterone as U.S. approval for adjuvant hormonal breast cancer.
Well before the U.N. because they've used a PRV.
And it's suggesting this could be an $11 billion plus product across the adjuvant and second
line, but mostly in adjuvant.
So then that seems to assume big board uptake.
I think the logic is that that could be used instead of someone using an aromatase and
a CDK4 for some of the patients.
So based on what you know about hormonal breast cancer, do you think that's plausible?
Do you think is it even from the end of this year you could see some pressure on CDK4?
K4 use because people instead would just do a CERN. So any thoughts on that, please?
Yeah, we don't see that in the same way. I mean, what we expect, continue to expect,
is that physicians will want to use something to ultimately impact the hormonal access and
then subsequently the cell cyclin-dependent kinase access, especially for patients that
we're talking about here, which are patients that are node zero, node one, node two, or more,
and have other risk factors that indicate they have a higher risk of recurrence of breast cancer.
So that's point one. That's all of our market research suggests that. And I think part of
the reason the major oral CERN companies are partnering with us to do combination studies
is they ultimately see it in a similar way as well. I can't comment on patients who are very
early or less high-risk early breast cancer patients. We used to call them kind of stage one.